kaaboodelmar.com 2015-03-22

# KAABOO Del Mar: Legal

The Website located at www.kaaboodelmar.com (the “Website”) is operated by HorsePower Entertainment, LLC (“HorsePower,” “us,” or “we”). This Privacy Policy discloses the privacy practices for the Website. 

You acknowledge that this Privacy Policy is part of our Site Terms of Use, and by accessing or using our site, you agree to be bound by all of its terms and conditions. If you do not agree to these terms, please do not access or use this site. 

We reserve the right to change this Privacy Policy at any time. Such changes, modifications, additions, or deletions shall be effective immediately upon posting. If we make material changes we will pose the revised policy here with an updated Effective Date. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this site and this Policy periodically, and to be aware of any modifications. Your continued use of the site after such modifications will constitute your: (a) acknowledgment of the modified Policy; and (b) agreement to abide and be bound by the modified Policy. 

1\. Types of Information Collected

We collect two types of information about our Website users: Personally Identifiable Information and Non­Personally Identifiable Information. 

Personally Identifiable Information:

This refers to information that lets us know the specifics of who you are. When you engage in certain activities on this site, such as registering as a user, ordering a product or service, submitting content and/or posting content in discussion forums or other public areas, entering a contest, filling out a survey, or sending us feedback, we may ask you to provide certain information about yourself by filling out and submitting an online form. It is completely optional for you to engage in these activities; however, we may ask that you provide us personal information, such as your first and last name, mailing address (including zip code), email address, employer, job title and department, telephone and facsimile numbers, and other personally identifying information. When ordering products or services on the site, you may be asked to provide a credit card number. Depending upon the activity, some of the information we ask you to provide is identified as mandatory and some as voluntary. If you do not provide the mandatory data with respect to a particular activity, you will not be able to engage in that activity. 

Non­Personally Identifiable Information:

This refers to information that does not by itself identify a specific individual. We gather certain information about you based upon where you visit on our site in several ways. This information is compiled and analyzed on both a personal and an aggregated basis. This information may include the Web site’s Uniform Resource Locator (“URL”) that you just came from, which URL you next go to, what browser you are using, and/or your Internet Protocol (“IP”) address. We may also collectstatistical information such as the number of pages of our Website that you view and which pages you access. 

2\. Collection Methods and Use of Information

We do not collect any Personally Identifiable Information about you unless you voluntarily provide it to us. You provide certain Personally Identifiable Information to us when you (a) register for our services and register your email address with us; (b) enter contests sponsored by us or one of our partners; (c) sign up for special offers from selected third parties; (d) send email messages, submit forms, or transmit other information by telephone or letter; or (e) submit your credit card or other payment information when ordering and purchasing products and services on our site. We may also collect information from you at other points on our site that state that such information is being collected. 

In addition, we may also collect, or our third­party ad server and/or content server may collect, certain Non­Personally Identifiable Information. We use your IP address to diagnose problems with our servers, software, to administer our site, and to gather demographic information. Our third­party ad servers will also provide us with summary, but not individual, reports that will tell us how many ads were presented and clicked upon at our site. 

We will use your Personally Identifiable Information for our general commercial purposes, including to provide our services to you, as required by our agreements with you. We may also use Personally Identifiable Information to enhance the operation of our site, fill orders, improve our marketing and promotional efforts, statistically analyze site use, improve our product and service offerings, and customize our site’s content, layout, and services. We may use Personally Identifiable Information to deliver information to you about our products and services and the products and services of others we think may be of interest to you and to contact you regarding administrative notices. We may also use Personally Identifiable Information to resolve disputes, troubleshoot problems, and enforce our agreements with you, including our Site Terms of Use, Sales Terms and Conditions, and this Privacy Policy. 

3\. Release of Information

We do not sell, trade, or rent your Personally Identifiable Information to others. We may share your Personally Identifiable Information with our affiliated companies for their commercial use. We do not share your information with any party, including affiliates, for their direct marketing use. 

We may reveal Personally Identifiable Information about you to unaffiliated third parties: (1) if you request or authorize it; (2) if the information is provided to help complete a transaction for you; (3) if the information is provided to comply with the law, applicable regulations, governmental and quasi­governmental requests, court orders or subpoenas, to enforce our Terms of Use or otheragreements, or to protect our rights, property or safety or the rights, property or safety of our users or others (e.g., to a consumer reporting agency for fraud protection etc.); (4) if the disclosure is done as part of a purchase, transfer or sale of services or assets (e.g., in the event that substantially all of our assets are acquired by another party, customer information may be one of the transferred assets); (5) if the information is provided to our agents, outside vendors or service providers to perform functions on our behalf (e.g., analyzing data, providing marketing assistance, providing customer service, processing orders, etc.); or (6) as otherwise described in this Privacy Policy. 

We will encourage our service partners to adopt and post privacy policies. However, the use of your Personally Identifiable Information by our service partners is governed by the privacy policies of those service partners and is not subject to our control. 

We may also provide Non­Personally Identifiable Information about our customers’ sales, traffic patterns, product usage statistics, and related site information to our affiliates and to third­partyies, but these statistics do not include any Personally Identifiable Information. 

When you submit your Personally Identifiable Information (i.e. your name, email address, etc.) in the discussion forums or other public areas on this site, that information, along with any information disclosed in your communication, can be collected and used by third parties and may result in unsolicited messages from third parties. Such activities are beyond our control and this Policy does not apply to such information. Any submissions to chat rooms or other public areas on this site are accepted with the understanding that they are accessible to all third parties. If you do not want your comments to be viewed by third parties, you are advised not to make any submissions. Please be careful and responsible whenever you are online. 

4\. Updating and Correcting Information

You have the ability to access and edit the Personally Identifiable Information that you have provided to us. You may change any of your Personally Identifiable Information in your account online at any time by accessing your account in accordance with instructions posted elsewhere on this site. You may also access and correct your personal information and privacy preferences by writing us at: 

    HorsePower Entertainment, LLC  
    
    5619 DTC Pkwy. Ste. 800  
    
    Greenwood Village, CO 80111  
    
    Attn: General Counsel  

Please include your name, address, and/or email address when you contact us. We encourage you to promptly update your Personally Identifiable Information if it changes. You may ask to have the information on your account deleted or removed; however, because we keep track of past transactions, you cannot delete information associated with past transactions on this site. In addition, it may be impossible to completely delete your information without some residual information because of backups.5. User Choices on Collection and Use of Information 

We may, from time to time, send you email regarding our products and services. In addition, if you indicated upon registration that you are interested in receiving offers or information from us and our partners, we may occasionally send you direct mail about products and services that we feel may be of interest to you. Only HorsePower (or agents working on behalf of HorsePower and under confidentiality agreements) will send you these direct mailings and only if you indicated that you do not object to these offers. If you do not want to receive such mailings, simply tell us when you give us your personal information. Or, at any time, you can easily edit your account information to no longer receive such offers and mailings. You may opt out of any promotional emails from us by following the instructions on the emails you receive. We will process your request promptly. Opting out of promotional emails will not prevent us from sending you transactional emails. 

You also have choices with respect to cookies, as described below. By modifying your browser preferences, you have the choice to accept all cookies, to be notified when a cookie is set, or to reject all cookies. If you choose to reject all cookies, some parts of our site may not work properly. 

6\. Protecting Children's Privacy

You must be at least 18 years old to have our permission to use this site. This Website is not designed nor intended to be attractive to use by children under the age of 18 ("Minors"). We do not knowingly collect information from minors. If you are under the age of 18, please do not submit any information to us. 

7\. Security of Information

We have reasonable administrative, technical and physical safeguards to protect your Personally Identifiable Information against unauthorized access, misuse, destruction or disclosure. You play a part in securing your information as well. Access to your Personally Identifiable Information is available through a password and unique customer ID selected by you. Any use of your customer ID and password is considered to be authorized by you. We recommend that you protect your customer ID and password and do not divulge them to anyone. 

In order to most efficiently serve you, credit card transactions and order fulfillment are handled by established third­party banking, processing agents and distribution institutions. They receive the information needed to verify and authorize your credit card or other payment information and to process and ship your order. We do not receive or keep your credit card information. 

Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet or any wireless network can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to protect your Personally Identifiable Information, youacknowledge that: (a) there are security and privacy limitations of the Internet which are beyond our control; (b) the security, integrity, and privacy of any and all information and data exchanged between you and us through this site cannot be guaranteed; and (c) any such information and data may be viewed or tampered with in transit by a third party. 

8\. Cookies

When you use our site we will store cookies on your computer in order to facilitate and customize your use of our site. A cookie is a small data text file, which a Web site stores on your computer’s hard drive (if your Web browser permits) that can later be retrieved to identify you to us. Our cookies store randomly assigned user identification numbers, the country where you are located, and your first name to welcome you back to our site. The cookies make your use of the site easier, make the site run more smoothly, and help us to maintain a secure site. You are always free to decline our cookies if your browser permits, but some parts of our site may not work properly in that case. Our Website may use the following types of cookies: 

Session cookies: These temporary cookies expire and are automatically erased whenever you close your browser window. We use session cookies to grant our users access to content and to enable actions they must be logged in to do. Persistent cookies: These usually have an expiration date in the distant future and remain in your browser until they expire or you manually delete them. We use persistent cookies to better understand usage patterns so we can improve the site for our customers. For example, we may use a persistent cookie to associate you with your user account or to remember that your choices on the Site, but this only works when cookies on our site are enabled. 

Third party cookies: We permit limited third parties to place cookies through theWebsite to provide us with better insights into the use of the Website or user demographics or to provide relevant advertising to you. These third parties may collect information about a consumer’s online activities over time and across different websites when he or she uses our Website. For example, we may use an outside ad serving company to display banner advertisements on our site. As part of their service, they will place a separate cookie on your computer. We will not provide any third­party ad server with any of your Personally Identifiable Information or information about your purchases. We and our third­party ad server will collect and use Non­Personally Identifiable Information about you, such as your IP address, browser type, the server your computer is logged onto, the area code and zip code associated with your server, and whether you responded to a particular ad. Other advertisers may also place banner ads on our site in the same manner as above, but we will not disclose any Personally Identifiable Information to them. 

We may also permit third party service providers to place cookies through our Site, as indicated above, to perform analytic or marketing functions where you are notified of them and you have consented to theusage. We do not control the use of such third party cookies or the resulting information and we are not responsible for any actions or policies of such third parties. Your use of our Site will be deemed to be your consent to the placement of cookies on your computer or other device. If you prefer not to receive cookies through our Site, you can set your browser to either reject all cookies, to allow only “trusted” websites to set them, or to accept only those cookies from those sites you are currently on. Unless you have adjusted your browser setting so that it will refuse cookies, our system will issue cookies when you log on to our Site and use it. 

We do not use technology that recognizes a “do­not­track” signal from your web browser. 

9\. Links to Third­Party Sites

When you use the Site or our service, you may be directed to other websites that are beyond our control. These may include merchant sites or payment sites. We may also allow thirds­party sites or applications to link to the Site. Other sites accessible through our site have their own privacy policies and data collection, use, and disclosure practices. Please consult each site’s privacy policy. We are not responsible for the policies or practices of third parties. 

10\. Contacting Us

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this site, please contact us by sending a letter to: 

    HorsePower Entertainment, LLC  
    
    5619 DTC Pkwy, Ste. 800  
    
    Greenwood Village, CO 80111  
    
    Attn: General Counsel  

Effective Date: October 16, 2014.
